What are you doing [sound of clearing throat]?
What are you idiots doing?
won.
What are you doing?   I am
practicing.
What are you practicing?  Tennis
of course.
Nothing will happen if you practice.
Whoever had to practice did it.
And she is our Sania Mirza, the pride of
India.  And
we are standing outside his house in
Dubai.  So let's go inside and have a look.
Lovely homes to are coming up and meeting
excited Sania Mirza.
Hello
welcome hi how are
you from oh my god so hot this is
Izhan hi how are
you?  How are you?  Hi Hi Hi
Nice to meet you
Hello Hi Very good Nice to meet you
Hi Izhan How are you?   He
is already eating snacks.
Okay come come come please come in what a
nice place man.   Thank
you.  Wow oh wow
I am so fascinated by just the
look of this home
whatever you see here is like I had to
really work hard for vegetarian [laughs]
but yahan pe mutton biryani bani hai because it's
a Hyderabadi house and one person it's not vegetable
happy [laughs]
my sister makes these videos with her
husband on Instagram and so many many
times I see the inspiration is both of you
she gives that like thing no inspiration
taken from [laughs]
anam she met you yes or she does 50 things out of which
one of the thing she does is copy you guys
[laughs]
but have you ever thought of starting a YouTube
I am running three businesses and taking
care of a kid which is a lot and
then I travel up obviously a lot to
India I am in India almost 8-10 days.
Here comes the
deserted Sania Mirza Tennis Academy in Hyderabad So then
I am
like you know only seven you know so
I am like that I
quit tennis one of the reasons was so that I could
spend more time with him now I will be doing
injustice if I do so many things
that required travel or please eat na have something
ye toh snack kyun
yaad aaya hai mujhe aaye hi hi challenge knock knock knock who is
there khuj khuj
[laughs] please take something so I was like I don't know where this
is going
[laughs]
let's not take khuj please take it [laughs]
so which class is Izaan in
Izaan has just graduated to the second
[laughs]
she already said I just come and say
hi and then I will be chilling in my room
so I said okay we will come visit you in the
room [laughs]
so let's let's do that let's do that
fun
aur humari aadhi zindagi idhar bhi idhar toh this is
Whatever the action is,
because like I said, I'm a very formal
person, otherwise I would have normally brought it here
if the camera wasn't there [laughs] I took it
there.  So, we just have this are TV
room, chilling room, here you know, everything.
Look at these inviting sofas, yah.   No
one should get up there.  Didn't even get up.  One
second I have to sit.
No, you lie down.  [laughter]
Just look at that.
No these are very very.
Cloud So From.   Or.
Oh!  Dude, obviously who will get up from here?
This is the place.
We watch cricket matches, watch TV shows
, chill at night.  And
when whoever comes to my yes, whatever
friends come, they just come and no one goes there.
Like, this is the most used
room.  I must.
Next time we come, we will come straight here.
You guys come next time.
I love this.
No one gifted this to me.  They made it
into a carpet.  It was a picture from
my Instagram, he took it out and
gifted me that.
So this one too, this is a painting.  This is
not a picture.  And it glows in the dark.   It is
not dark right now but gloss in but when you
go closer then you will realize that it is okay.
Stay till night.  We'll
see when it gets dark [laughs].  Isn't it
?  If you stay till night, it will become dark.
Please, everyone came here just like this.
So I have a hidden talent.  Should I call it talent, should I
call it hobby?
I have done up the house.
Or there was nothing in it so we did this a
guest room.  So it's
very caring and soothing.  Isn't it?
Or I just thought you know we make an
experiment with our own house.
Whatever means you can put something.
Love this bed.  Like the sandals, the
light fittings are very cute to me
and there is a washroom thing,
washroom I did not do anything [laughs]
washroom is not clean toh hum nahi dikhayenge it is
clean but I did not do it and then I will just
show you outside
I love this, take care beautiful
and this actually we go and see this
actually Salman had gifted me.
So personally made it for you.  Wow lucky you.
Next time, give me something from Meethi too,
friend [laughs]
As you can see, nothing is cooked in the kitchen.
We play games here.
Oh my God.
This kitchen outside is actually a kitchen.
So but this is a three in one table.  So This
Becomes Air Hockey and Table Tennis.  Another
thing also happens.  I think it's made of smokers or something.
Inside Hockey.
But this is inside him.   Does
this mean it was kept in the kitchen?
No, this is not used in the kitchen.  This is the show kitchen.
It just makes coffee.  Nothing else happens around here [laughter].
This is an outside.
It's Actually Quite Nice.  It is here.
Oh wow.  If you
come forward on this side, you won't be able to tell
how much space is there at the back, so that's a little gazebo,
this is obviously Izhaan's play area,
yes, when he was little,
we were also in the mud, it's so difficult to
maintain the outdoor area,
either the main kitchen is there where the food is
cooked, excited, it's better that we have a
bigger space, I feel like boys thrive in
space,
if he likes football, then
obviously he needs some space, he
plays tennis, he plays football, he plays tennis,
I make him play because
[laughs] I want, I want, why,
Izhaan was playing FIFA, so he was playing
with Sunil Chhatri, okay, think, I
met Sunil at an event, and I said, Sunil is always complaining that
you are missing the goals in FIFA [laughs],
so I told Sunil, so I made a
video for him, in that Sunil said, I
hate you are always complaining that I am missing
your goal, I hope we can practice together
[laughs], he was  So surprise he was so
surprise
missing [laughs]
always missing in fun
[laughs]
we're coming up warning
Izan's room this is exactly what I would have
wanted my room to be when I was a kid
[music]
and here Izan has swimming
pools.
But it is said that a child should play every sport.
His different skills
develop.   Did
you hear?  [laughter]
He just plays drums.   The
poor guy is saying that all this has happened.   The
game is paused.
Son, you play.
Okay, we are leaving.
Yes.   Ok, bye.
[laughs]
Okay,
okay, [laughs]
I totally understand.
Poor guy.
This is my bedroom.
Wow.
This was my color.  I wanted it to be.
What's up friend?  Wow.
Well sometimes you forget, you forget
who this is?  [laughs] I'm Sania.
I actually stole this from a hotel and brought it on my own bed.
[laughs]
Hey Sania, how many cities have you travelled to in your life
?  How many passport
booklets do you have?  There is a lot.
Still there
is a lot.  Actually I went to counselling only yesterday.  I had to get a
new passport for my region, but I had
six in my head, Mangal, till now I had six,
seven, so many doubles, double double
double,
but our countries were always on repeat every year.
Because every year during the Australian Open
we play the Australian Open.  During Wimbledon, he
plays Wimbledon.  And then so on.
So we do the I've done
the same countries for 20
years.  So, maybe like 25
years?
Tell me how does it feel to go?  You go and
you play on the courts at Wimbledon.  How did it
feel?  And you one Wimbledon?  Wow.
No, actually when I was small
everyone used to taunt me.  Do you think you'll
play Wimbledon one day?
So do you think that when you told my parents,
you guys went mad?  You are
travelling around the world with her.   You are
investing all your money in him.  You are doing everything.
Till date has anyone become a tennis player or will she become one or will she
play or this is for us, yes our daughter will do it
and I mean they had their dream so no matter what I want that
Wimbledon
stage is very very special because I used to get
taunts for that, do you ever
think that if you play Wimbledon, then Wimbledon was
not played at all, we won
Sheikh [laughs]
I am a huge tennis fan, it's huge
tennis.   The
Only Sport I Ever Watch: Tennis.  Only
Sport.  And yours is the four hands,
it is like one of the best
strongest.  [laughter] Yes, man.  So in
fact Dubai was open.  Once I
saw you had I think you she's playing
a world number one or somebody has
so I one I cause she had just one US Open.
That was my first break through in the year 2000.
I saw that match years ago.  And I saw
your four hands boom.  It was like wow man.
So strong na the forehand [laughs] amazing
thank you come this
Abhinash he took this picture
or it was just a shoot and he just Izhaan
in my lap he let me take a photo and he just took this
so sweet this is a prayer room I
feel like there is a coming energy as soon as it is coming
but here they read Quran,
read namaz anybody that comes we in
Ramadan we have a jamaat jamaat so hum log sare jitna bhi
family and friends hain we all break our
fast and then we do like a you know jamaat
together and stuff.  So this
is the Padmashree actually.
Padmashree and Padma Bhushan
Padma Bhushan is not here in Hyderabad
but Padmashree is here.
So let me tell you about Padmashree, Padma Bhushan and
Arjuna Award and many others.  Khel Ratna
Butler also Khel Ratna.
Thank you so much.  Thank you so much.  [laughter]
I'm tearing up.
Only Games That We Know To Play A Blame
Games.  [laughter] Yes,
old married couple but beautiful.
Yeah, so here are some trophies I put, but these are
like the medals from Gongzao 2010
[nasal sound].
Inshyeon 2014 Asian Games medals.   There
is someone else there,
someone says there is someone else there.
This is from Doha.  Doha Asian Games 2006
Wow.
I remember you from this time.  You know this is this is
or 2015
these are actually you get the bronze medal for the Wimbledon semi-finals.
Wow!
Let's see your Wimbledon medal brother.
Dude I have to touch this.  [laughter]
And it's just lying here casually.
And this is the last Australian Open
final.  I retired on 23 February and
played the 23 Australian Open final in January.
Good.
So here are
half the medals.  Half are there.
Archana ji, you will understand why I
tell you the maximum time.
I also want that cloth, friend.  [laughs]
It
's a dream for any woman, man, it's a
dream to have such a big room to get ready and do
makeup.
How many clothes do you have?
No clothes,
friend, you are not alone.
No, she is not alone.
Yes mom, you too must have the same number of clothes.
If not,
this is the plan.
We work.
Yes, we have to go out.  [laughter]
Excuse me.
You don't go out wearing pants or shirt.
Exactly [laughter]
what about them?  If it has to be shaved for two consecutive days, then
shave again.  We have
makeup,
open it?
Well I thought
slide slide you will appreciate that.
Wow!   I
have bags.
Or [laughs] I have that bag
up there too.
I think the left shoe left shoe has to be
you will love [ __ ]
oh I love this
oh my god [laughs]
or you are wishing that it keeps fitting you yes
this is a very nice and large size
or or sea wardrobe itni badi lag chauri wardrobes vanity
bahut pyara sa vanity hai you know how many covers she has in her
room one two three four
gin ke nazar na aana.  Yes I saw this
[laughs] this
is the quantity
oh this is the lazy basket I thought I had to
give things below
Sania
you can send your phone in this [laughs]
hello ana ana upstairs [laughs]
I love this when
you have this high ceiling then you have
like a hole in the this is the best [laughs]
I love this so this
ride behind you is actually the
actual cloth from the Kaaba which is or
so the actual cloth it is on the side of it
which it is part of the pillow so somebody
gifted me for my birthday.  So they change it
every year that black cloth of
his that one a little bit this was a cloth or
that is from it actually.
And what are you writing here?
This is a prayer for protection.  Okay or
Oh Wow!  Please give me all this food,
oh my God!  No no,
we are Hyderabadis.
We don't give that much food.  [laughs]
You Hyderabadis have made Punjabis go crazy when it comes to
food.
If I had known there was so much to eat,
I wouldn't have eaten lunch.
I told horp ok
guys knocknock.
Who is there?   To
express any doubt.
I am not saying anything.  I am feeling scared.
[laughter]
Knock knock.
She's not saying who is there?  She Saying.
Yes.  Who is that
Dubai baren
Dubai baren Dubai baren
Oh Dubai
baren we are playing and having fun
oh my god papa
I met you for the first time but it's too bad
[laughs]
[laughs] the more
criticism comes the
better it is for me
you know how to speak Hyderabadi
for example if like the joke that you would have said if I want to say something
Hyderabadi
kya baingan ki baant kar raha hai [laughs]
kya baant ki baant kar raha hai like what
Rabesh [laughs]
what should I say
kya baant ki baant kar raha hai like they make no
one is right but
[laughs] Hyderabadi understand kya baant ki
baant
papa ke haath jo bolenge
kya baant kar raha hai [laughs]
one of the main reasons I became a world
champion because I am a home maker which was
my mom pushed me to become one so being a
home maker is like that
and if a home maker can do that then imagine
what people can do so you should
really not underestimate  And Bilin
's, no, you don't do anything, well,
you
call yourself a housewife at home, many women look at you, at least you call yourself a
homemaker,
you say housewife, you say
housewife, well you don't do anything,
oh how much does one become a wife, so my I mean my
mom works, but not like
my dad was in construction and
stuff, but my mom used to run a printing press.
So, I mean at that point we all had to
work.  So when I was born my
dad had a scooter.  So that was the
background, we came from, you know, middle
class, of late, at best, middle
class at that time.  And then when I was
born my mom said that I will not make my daughter
sit on a scooter.  So he went and got
some fifth hand Maruti and something okay.
[laughs]
So cute
or I mean that time pe purani bilkul katara
but she was like nahi scooter pe main bachchi
ko nahi baitha I
want to meet the mom now more sia mom ko meet karna chahti hoon
or so that is how my journey started and then
my parents were watching one day match
of Wimbledon
Steffi Graf vs Cosita Martins I
believe
final was going on and then my dad said that what if
one day we see Sania play on this
court then my mom just said she was
pregnant with my sister and my mom said that I will give
my life for it.
Oh that was
the moment where they were like now
we should call them tennis players, that is we will do everything,
look at the story,
what an inspiring story, what an
inspiring story, what a lovely story,
such committed mom and dad should be there.
You guys are not there.
We ourselves procured the land for SMTA which was built in Hyderabad.  We have our
own
land and it was our dream because when I used to
play tennis,
we used to play on cow dung courts
because those were not there, so we had to
take tetanus injections to play, so
from there obviously that was
the dream, not the reality anyway, so that was
the story, so as a family, our
dream was that this generation will not have to know this, so
we made a four-year plan and we met an
SMDA.  There are 12 tennis courts there.
We have tournaments there.  There
is an Olympic side swimming pool there.  Like a
clubhouse and staying is.  Like it's a full
fledge.  So my mom is actually running it.
Full
yes.  That the Five Stay Women Again?  [laughter]
My momma is fully running it.
When did you first feel that now I know this is
mine I am going to make it.   I
think I was actually 12 years old.  When
I was in the Under 14 and Under 16 Nationals on the same
day,
I was 12 years old, so I vividly remember
that day that I was like,
hey, you know, I'm quite good at this, like,
I'm okay, not quite literally like
[laughs] that, you know, because it never happened that
our family sat together and
said, okay, from today, we will become professional tennis
players, that never happened,
well,
we just kept doing things
or it just kind of happened. Another fun fact is that
I was a huge geek, so I did
n't want to play tennis because I wanted 100%
attendance and I wanted to get nothing less than 95%,
and I would cry if I got one, so I was a very
big nerd.  I used to know
like pages, if you had asked me on the 75th page what is
this whole rota main maar ke jaati
[laughs]
this is revealing brother,
actually a scholar I was
not a scholar, I was a rota
master [laughs]
so in those days my headmistress of the
school convinced me
that you should go out and play and you know
who was the head mistress,
the great Pataudi sister,
Mrs. Ali Khan or
well
she told me that my brother did this and you know he also
means at that point you don't
understand you are small.   You are.
So guys desert is here.
Guys, look here comes the dessert.  [laughter]
She's not eating this.
She is not eating.
He has not eaten sugar for a long time.
[laughter]
Oh, I'm going to get that tea.
My hand accidentally slipped.  And it came into my hands.
No problem [laughs].  Neither of these matters.   No no this you know
me and Diya have always been from the same school.
What happened once?  Somebody Came and Told My
Mom Congratulations
My Mom for Me [laughs]
She won the Asia Pacific.  Sanya
[laughs]
Mr.
Oh, so nice.  How was the pageant my mom which
pageant?  [laughter]
Which pageant in between, Mr. Sania?  And then my mom and then they were like
we are right and she's like no, no,
my daughter's place is like [laughs]
my parents I don't know how but they found a very good
balance
of pushing me enough yet not making me feel like their life
depends on it like for
example when I used to lose I didn't cry
when I was little
all my parents used to ask my parents
why doesn't she cry she doesn't care what does it she doesn't
cry you know my
father always said tennis is a very good part of
life but it's not your life not your
life very good thing so it's a very good
part we are putting in a lot of effort but
your life won't end if you
say mature thing in tennis but we I didn't understand that
when I was little I did
n't understand its depth so
what they used to do when I used to lose a match
or I used to win a match and we were
out of Hyderabad we always had
ice cream after the match  We used to go to eat but when we lost,
we would definitely go to eat ice cream.   That was they never said it
but I understood that they taught me that the
love that they have for me was not dependent
on my winners and losers.  But I felt that it took so much
pressure of me during my playing
days, ah I was thrilled under pressure.  But when there was
a pressure situation in a match, I
would be like I will take it.  I was like
what's the worst that can happen.  I will
lose the match.
Awesome.  So That Came From This.
But whatever I have said to you, whenever
[sound of clearing throat] I have met
you on Kapil Sharma's stage, I have
observed that how is this person?  So there is a
little bit of psychology involved.  You know,
you are very strong internally.   There is
no such profession in the world.  Not even
you have any profession.  Where
you lose every day, you win.
Daily.
No, this happens to those who are jurors too.
[laughter]
Yeah, man.  Today my luck has run out today [laughs] I
just said the dialogue,
what are you doing with the banyan tree,
but there is no other actual profession
[laughs]
that is legal
and appreciated
and respected [laughs] and respected
and respected [laughs]
okay guys thanks for
welcome to cheap coffee with gun
where you are not going to get anything.
Great
you can you can have some cheese please.
I gave it to you, brother.
Please consider it your home [laughs], it's all
okay.
That's why he is saying it is cheap.
We're going to do a rapid fire around and my
co-host Ayushmann Sethi is going to start.
Oh.
If Not Tennis Then What?
Interiors, Interior Designers.
I-H Hyderabad or Dubai?
No, Hyderabad.
I am a Hyderabadi girl.
Indian food or English type of food?  Desi
food, Indian food.
Late nights, or early mornings.
Late Night I'm a Nocturnal Person.  And I do that
opposite to what my career has been.
[laughter] I'm a nocturnal person.
Travel and stay at home
stay at home.
Travel can not even outside my.  [laughter]
Fedra or Nadal.   I can't say a
suck one.  Djokovic I will say?
Oh.  [laughter]
Oh!  Alcras and Sinon.
Alcras.   Yes.
I like little.   Yes
, yes.
Camera check.  Something you're terrible at something I can't draw anything
my cat is like
to circles and [laughs]
like that how bad have
you ever protested to no one you then
speak to you saying oh yes we were here
and you would have no idea
ya or every day almost it happens I do it all the time all the
time I can't remember names
firstly and looks I used to be better I
think no I'm older and using it
if you're old then hum toh tuha how do you have
it?  How do you say that we
just act well?
Act good so career
this is going to happen next time I meet him.  [laughter]
They'll be like I took a photo with you.   I
wore it there at the airport.
Yes, I shook hands with you at that airport.
I said I don't know.
I wore a green shirt.  I don't know how
[laughs] I got to say yes,
of course it's more
effort to put [laughs].
Coaching or commentary?
Between them, I'm not coaching, but I actually do this
initiative called The Next Set, where I
help the top eight to 10 girls in the
country.  So I'm mentoring I'll set
coaching.
So mentoring
it's called the next set.
Next set.
And do you remember any hidden talent like party
tricks or something?
Party The Trick Is Only That I Don't Go To
Party.  [laughs]
What about makeup or no makeup.
I prefer no makeup.
Makeup.
But unfortunately now we have reached the age where we
need makeup.
[laughter]
But you'll be wilder than ever.
You know, right?
Whatever you are doing is working.
Whatever I am doing it's working.  Thank
you.
I live this.   I don't
want it.
Should have
reduced it.
You also get this with it.  [laughter] It
's very cheap, brother.   The
reason is over guys.  Thank you please.   Right here, right here,
brother.
Like, share, subscribe will
be said in Hyderabadi.  How will you say it?
Yes, how will you say it?   Do
whatever you want, however you want, like, share,
subscribe and definitely watch this episode.
What brinjal are you talking about, Papa?  [laughs]
Baingan baingan ke bhaata.   I
like brinjal.
Hey dad, what about brinjal?  [laughter] What?
Guys, this is injustice to me,
boss.
Like brinjal.  [Laughter]